Good morning. Good morning, everybody. It's early over here in the East, but I get up early
because there's a lot of work to do. So shout out to everybody who's up. Hello in Australia.
Good morning. Good morning. Today is the birthday of the late Fred Hampton Jr. I mean,
the late Fred Hampton Sr. And I want to start our day with his words. I do have Goku. I do have
Goku posts up there. And I got Aang over here. I got Aang right next to Martin. I mean, next to Malcolm.
So for those who don't know, Fred Hampton was the chairman of the Black Panther Party of Chicago.
And what a lot of people also don't know about the Black Panther Party is that every faction of the
Black Panther Party wasn't the same. Also, however, however, the Black Panther Party was not solely
just a armed militia to challenge and police the police. The Black Panther Party was aspiring
to have coalition across a shared interest of socialism. And thus, when I see the constant effort
of folks to ignore liberalism in the face of liberalism, I know that they have become disconnected
from the goal of the very folks that they claim to be, you know, fighting on the backs of.
When you see folks say, I vote because my ancestors voted. They nine times out of 10 do not know why
their ancestors, they vote because they died because our ancestors died to vote. Nine times out of 10,
they do not know why their ancestors had to die to vote. Their ancestors weren't dying to vote.
Their ancestors ended up being murdered in the process of actualizing their rights as American
citizens, among which was voting, as well as riding in desegregated vehicles, public vehicles, you know,
like the Freedom Rides, eating at desegregated counters. So when we are talking about these next phase of our
existence in this nation and on this planet, we have to invoke the words of a Fred Hampton
and ignore the teaching that has been happening over the past 40 years. They assassinated people
like Fred Hampton so they could teach you not to continue the legacy of individuals like Fred Hampton.
And anybody who is telling you otherwise is not worth your time. Fred Hampton said,
we don't think you fight fire with fire. We fight fire with water. We don't fight racism with racism.
We fight racism with solidarity. We don't fight capitalism with black capitalism. We fight
capitalism with socialism. I want you to think about this. And I want you to think about how many
examples of this you, I mean, I want you to think about how many examples you have seen that counter this.
And I want you to think about how many examples felt good in your body. Did they feel right in your body? Did they,
did they feel like vengeance or did they feel like peace? One of the biggest misconceptions
assumptions is that there has not been a consistent violent war against coalition against the empire
since World War II. So many of us only exist in the timeline of our own lives.
So for instance, anybody who says this ain't our fight, they voted for such and such is completely
disconnected from the fact that since 1965, there has been a concerted effort to undermine any effort
at coalition building. Anybody who says I'm just focused on black people does not understand that,
you know, who else is focused on black people? The same people that got you focused on black people
and all of us who have understood that the fight lasts and has been lasting understand
that in order for there to ever, ever, ever be peace ever, we're going to have to do what Fred
Hampton was speaking about. Fred Hampton was 21 when they took him out because they saw that he understood.
I wasn't born when Fred Hampton died. I like to think that any of us who were born after Fred Hampton
may have a piece of Fred Hampton in us. I like to think that we are born from the stardust of that
which disseminated before us. I like to think that we are given the example. So there really is no
reason not to exist in it once we know. Now there are things, there are impediments that prevent us
from being able to exist in that. Yes, there's a society that suggests that there's only one way to
exist and that if you do not exist like that, then you are a problem. There's an internet that
constantly has us in a state of toxicity, fighting, bickering. There's an internet that exists in exactly
the same format, in exactly the same format as the effort of COINTELPRO to disassemble any movement
that was working towards black liberation. And that format is to supplant and implant
disingenuousness, disinformation to disconnect. Here's an example. So you hear about ADOS, right?
The American descendants of slavery. Now I have been called all kinds of names and told all kinds of,
you know, go back to Grenada, blah, blah, blah, blah from ADOS, right? My mother is from Grenada. My father
is from Boston, Massachusetts, and is the descendant of slaves from Maryland and Arkansas.
I've done the genealogy. This is a fact. ADOS is constantly moving in a, moving from a place of
reparations should only be owed to the, to the descendants of, of American slaves. I mean, of American
slavery. And this, um, mindset constantly pushes a goal of denigrating immigrants. I have never in my life
seen a Caribbean or an African descendant or first generation with both parents from those places
make a demand on American reparations for slavery. Never. I have never in my life.
Yet I am constantly seeing a grounding from these organizations in, in a possession, in a fight to
possess something that no one is trying to take from them. I've, I've never, I've never seen that.
Now, I have seen faceless bot accounts do that. Never in my life. But I am constantly seeing ADOS and
FBA in a fight for their lives to, to, to, to make a claim of their relevance against immigrants. And yet I've
never, and, and yet I've never seen immigrants seeking to claim that which they possess rightfully.
I haven't. Constantly told, you know, only, only descendants of slavery deserve, deserve, um, reparations.
Okay. Yes. American descendants of slavery do deserve reparations. I'm not confused. I mean,
that is a fact. There is no, there is no refuting that. Why would a Grenadian slave get reparations
from the United States? No, they would get it from England. I should be getting reparations from England
and the United States. So that's an example though, of the disinformation. That's an example of the
discord that is supplanted to continue to keep the diaspora from being connected. Pen Africanists
believe this. I believe this. Fred Hampton died because of this. On this day of Fred Hampton's birth,
I want you all to consider what are the ways in which you are embodying your ancestors.
I want you to consider the ways in which you are shifting with your new knowledge and information.
And I want you to be honest with yourself. I don't want you to try to protect your ego.
I want you to be honest with yourself. Like people try to shave me for things that I'm honest about.
I used to be somebody who believed in Democrats. I used to believe the lies. That is the goal of the
lies. They spend millions and billions of dollars for you to believe this. And there are black people
that sit up on this internet every single day who believe it too. And in their best interests,
think that they are rallying an army. They're not, but they do think so. They do. And, and, and it is going
to be us unlearning that which has been sent to us and, and taught to us to pacify us that will be the
factor to change things. They gave you Democrats. So they, so that they could take your dissent.
They gave you Democrats so they could take your dissent. They gave you capitalism
to encourage your capitulation. They gave you black excellence to silence black resistance.
They did. And if we really understood history, we would understand how many of the things that we
think happened in a timeline this long happened in a timeline this long. That is the biggest lie
that many of us don't understand. We don't understand how close together things happened
in understanding that that closeness is an indic is indicative of the goal of the action.
Don't ask me what the path forward is when I'm literally sitting here telling you what the path
forward is. Stop doing that shit. It's fucking idiotic. For instance, Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.
was assassinated on April 4th, 1968. Fred Hampton, Fred Hampton was assassinated on December 4th, 1969.
Bobby Kennedy was assassinated June 6th, 1968. Patrice Lumumba was assassinated June 17th,
1961. But Thomas Sankara. No, that's not who I'm thinking of. Sankara was 87.
Who am I thinking of right now? And who they could not assassinate, they imprisoned. They imprisoned.
When we don't understand the overlap of all of these things, we put them in silos.
We don't understand timelines. So we don't see because we're not allowed the opportunity to do
pattern recognition. The late 60s to the mid 70s were another revolution. And the fact that it's not
framed that way for you is by design. It stops after the civil rights movement. However, after the civil
rights movement was a revolution, it was a revolution, it was an intellectual revolution
led by people like Fred Hampton. The intellectual revolution was also a spiritual revolution.
That revolution was one of self-love, self-knowledge, self-awareness.
There was the black college movement that said, we're going to go all, we're going to go to all of
our colleges and demand black studies. The Latinos did the same thing. The Chicanos did the same thing.
All of this was happening in one timeframe, y'all. And then it was shut down. The black arts movement of
the 70s where edutainment was born was a concerted effort by black creatives to say, we are going to
take the teachings of individuals like Fred Hampton and immerse it into our art so that our people are
being educated at the same time they're being entertained. And all of this was shut down.
And then like Sly Rice 313 said, next thing you know, you had heroin and you had
crap in the 80s. And the reason I think so many people don't want to admit to this is because they
want to believe in a false sense of security that somehow they are safe or that somehow this has all
been by happenstance. Because if they can believe that, then they can believe in their own futility.
But the truth of the matter is that there was a revolution. And I need you, I need you to know that
because the goal of apathy and cynicism is to convince you that there cannot be a better one.
The goal of apathy and cynicism is to convince you that there is no hope.
And if you don't believe that there ever was one, then you won't believe that there can be one.
You won't study and learn from it to see how you can do better at it this time.
So I refuse, I refuse to ignore the possibility. And Fred Hampton was one who showed us
that there is no age limit. That wisdom comes in all packages. That coalition building is not just
some cute leftist ideal. It is a necessity. It's a necessity. Why you think in Star Wars,
the rebel forces is a body? Anybody? In Star Wars, the rebel forces is all flavors, honey.
It's vital. Yes, Luli Melody. So we must remember the words of the late Fred Hampton who was born on this day.
We don't think you fight fire with fire. We fight fire with water. We won't fight racism with racism.
We fight racism with solidarity. We won't fight capitalism with black capitalism. We fight capitalism with socialism.
Now, for those who don't know, I do my show of views for Amanda Land every Wednesday at 10 a.m. Eastern right here on YouTube,
Amanda Seals TV. So you can go over to YouTube and subscribe. And this is the type of stuff we own.
You can also subscribe to my Patreon. And if you can't do either of those, I hope that you will be working with your own communities.
And I want to remind you that community does not have to be a bunch of people. Community can just start as your group chat.
And saying, what are, you know, let's make a concerted effort to put time to talking about things that we may not have been talking about.
Like, I have people that I literally once a month get up with just to talk black things.
That's it. We literally get together once a month just to talk black things.
And what are black things? Black things does not mean to just talk about black people.
But to talk about where we are mentally, physically, individually, politically, communally, internationally.
They're parents. So we talk about where they are parentally.
So, you know, someone here said, Fred Hampton and the Black Panthers did not do it the correct way.
I would implore you to change your language.
However, and they said this is a spiritual battle against Esau, Edom, not a physical one.
It is both. How can you say it's not a physical one when they are murdering black people in droves?
It is both.
How can we talk about spiritual when we know that there's no coincidence that every expression of gods all over the world
has always involved some type of weaponry has always involved some type of weaponry?
Always.
They either got some type of bow and arrow or some type of special magic cape or nine arms.
You know, they got a dog head.
They always got some type of capability to protect.
Always.
Because the spirit is, I believe, that which understands that there will always be a need to protect.
Even if you think about our bodies, we have cells that are meant to populate and then we have cells that are meant to take motherfuckers out.
In nature, you see the same thing.
Today, I'll be working on a new project and my Patreon subscribers will get the opportunity to watch.
Don't quote the Bible to me, please.
Please do not quote the Bible to me.
Don't quote the Torah to me.
Don't quote none of them books to me.
As if, like, case closed.
If you want to quote a book to me and say, you know, this is a quote from this book that inspires me
or this is a quote from this book that speaks to me, you need to give, oops, did someone just tell me to relax?
Ooh, you can go.
Don't ever tell me to relax.
So, when people come with the, you know, I'm quoting this book and so now that shuts everything down,
I'm not interested in those types of interactions.
If you, if you're, if you seek guidance from those books, if those books inspire you,
if they give you a grounding, I understand.
I respect that.
But when people come with the, now that I've said this, now what?
I'm like, please.
Please.
No, he did tell someone else.
He told someone else she's not preaching.
Relax.
So, don't tell them to relax and don't tell me to relax.
Okay.
And hello, Ahmed.
If you have not checked out the latest episode of Small Doses Podcast with Ahmed Kabbalo,
please do for an incredible interview around African Stream, the platform that was created
and deplatformed by Democrats because it was speaking about U.S. imperialism.
And speaking the truth about the continent from the voices of people on the continent, as it should.
Okay.
So, you get to be removed because you're annoying.
Um, so, again, today is Fred Hampton's birthday.
I hope that you will take a moment to, to duck, duck, go.
Fred Hampton, um, already blocked Yoko Nomi.
Blocked.
Um, and learn about this brother's vision because I want you to understand why he was assassinated.
I want you to understand why he was assassinated and I want you all to get very curious.
Curious about socialism.
I do not offer mentoring because I do that goddang, all goddang day over here.
If I offered mentoring, I would never have a time to myself to create, to be quite honest.
You know?
So, I want, I want us to be willing to engage in learning about that which we have been lied to about.
So, shout out to all of my SEAL squad members, the Patreon members who will be joining us today, uh, for the behind the scenes of my new project that I'm working on.
Ooh, that's what's up, Kay.
Looking forward to, to, to charting that course.
I could not figure out my costume for the life of me, but then it hit me this morning what my costume is.
So, I'm excited to go and, um, get that going.
Um, everyone, remember that, uh, you are your limitations.
You are your limitations.
You are limited by that which you take in, by who you listen to.
If you have been, if you, if you've been following the same accounts now that you were two years ago, you're limited.
You're limited.
There's no reason you should still be following the same accounts that you were two years ago.
The world has changed so drastically that you should have as well.
So, you guys, it is Saturday.
Stay lifted.
Please keep me covered in your thoughts.
Um, and venture to impress yourself.
Tired of the people.